en:
  mrkhanh: "Mr. Khanh Mata"
  mrnguyen: "Mr. Tran Thao Nguyen"
  khanhphone: "096 440 3444"
  khanhmail: "radnvk@gmail.com"
  khanhchatwork: "KhanhMata"
  nguyenphone: "096 287 1867"
  nguyenmail: "nguyen@gmail.com"
  nguyenchatwork: "857585"
  iteampro: "iTeam production"
  title: "Framgia E-Testing System"
  hello: "Hello world"
  name_system: "Framgia E-Testing"
  title_system: "Framgia E-Testing System"
  welcome: "Welcome to the Framgia E-learning System"
  warning_login: "Please sign up or sign in to view!!!"
  fb: "Facebook"
  gethelp: "To get help on this page, see us at"
  khanhmata: "Khanh Mata"
  nguyen: "Tran Thao Nguyen"
  rubyrailstutor: "Ruby on Rails Tutorial"
  account: "Account"
  contribute: "Contribute Questions"
  home: "Home"
  help: "Help"
  about: "About"
  designedby: "Designed by"
  aboutus: "(a.k.a Khanh Nguyen) and"
  specialthank: "Specially thanks to Michael Hartl</a>for the "
  contact: "Contact"
  contactus: "Contact us"
  phone: "Phone:"
  mail: "Mail:"
  chatworkidct: "Chatwork:"
  sign_up: "Sign up"
  sign_up_user: "signup"
  sign_in: "Sign in"
  new_user: "New user?"
  categories: "Categories"
  create: "Create my account"
  creates: "Create"
  helloname: "Hello %{name}"
  error_content: "The form contains"
  not_found: "Not fount"
  error: "Error"
  footer: "Framgia"
  modal_title: "Create Subject"
  submit_button: "submit_button"
  chatworkid: "Chatwork ID"
  confirmation: "Confirmation"
  submit: "Submit"
  submit_button: "Create"
  profile: "Profile"
  login: "Log in"
  logout: "Log out"
  iteam: "An e-testing system designed by iTeam"
  news: "News"
  etesting: "Framgia Test System"
  etest: "Etesting"
  users: "Users"
  unsuccess_login: "Invalid email/password combination"
  welcome: "Welcome to Framgia E-testing System!"
  please_login: "Please log in!"
  remembercomputer: "Remember me on this computer"
  signupnow: "Sign up now!"
  form_error_messages: "The form contains %{plural}."
  error_text: "error"
  flash:
    success:
      created_subject: "Created subject successfully!"
      created_exam: "Created exam successfully!"
      contributed_question: "Contributed question successfully!"
    danger:
      created_subject: "Created subject failed!"
      created_exam: "Created exam failed!"
      contributed_question: "Contributed question failed!"
  admin:
    subjects:
      subjects:
        create_subject: "New Subject"
        delete: "Delete"
        delete_subject_confirm: "Are you sure you want to delete this subject? This action cannot be undone!"
        index: "Index"
        name: "Subject's Name"
        question_number: "Questions"
        duration: "Duration"
        actions: "Actions"
      new:
        cancel_button: "Cancel"
        create_button: "Create"
        save_button: "Save changes"
      form:
        cancel_button: "Cancel"
      edit:
        cancel_bt: "Cancle"
        edit: "Edit"
      index:
        title: "All subjects"
    questions:
      answer: "Answer"
      edit:
        edit_question: "Edit question"
        edit_button: "Edit"
      new:
        suggest_question: "Suggest Question"
        create_button: "Save"
      form:
        question_content: "Type question's content here..."
        add_answer: "Add answer"
        submit_button: "Suggest"
        question_content_error: "At least 5 characters"
      answer_fields:
        answer_content: "Type answer's content here..."
        remove_answer: "Remove"
        answer_content_error: "Answer must have content"
        answer: "Answer"
      index:
        suggested_questions: "Suggested Questions"
        title: "Contributed questions"
        delete_question_confirm: "Do you want delet this question?"
        new_question: "New question"
        question: "Question"
        subject_name: "Subject's name"
        answer_type: "Answer's type"
        status: "Status"
        content: "Content"
        type_answer: "Type Answer"
        edit: "Edit"
      errors:
        must_more_one: "must has more than 1 answer"
        must_has_correct_answer: "must has at least 1 correct answer"
      question:
        delete_question_confirm: "Are you sure you want to delete this user?"
        index:
          new_question: "New Question"
        new:
          create_button: "Save"
  exams:
    questions:
      save: "Save"
      checked: "Checked"
      finish: "Finish"
      finish_confirm: "Are you sure you want to finish this exam? This action cannot be undone!"
    index:
      start_button: "Start"
      view_button: "View"
      created_date: "Created Date"
      subject_name: "Subject's name"
      status: "Status"
      duration: "Duration"
      question_number: "Question number"
      time: "Spent Time"
      marks: "Marks"
      create_button: "Create Exam"
      exam_list: "Examination List"
      title: "Exams"
    answers:
      content_answer: "Your answer"
      content_answer_holder: "Type your answer here..."
      content_answer_hint: "This is a text answer. Please type your answer to the above field."
  labels:
    status:
      exam:
        start: "start"
        testing: "testing"
        uncheck: "uncheck"
        checked: "checked"
        inactive: "inactive"
  questions:
    answer: "Answer"
    new:
      suggest_question: "Suggest Question"
    form:
      question_content: "Type question's content here..."
      add_answer: "Add answer"
      submit_button: "Suggest"
    answer_fields:
      answer_content: "Type answer's content here..."
      remove_answer: "Remove"
      answer_content_error: "Answer must have content"
      answer: "Answer"
    index:
      suggested_questions: "Suggested Questions"
      new_question: "New question"
      question: "Question"
      subject_name: "Subject's name"
      answer_type: "Answer's type"
      status: "Status"
    errors:
      must_more_one: "must has more than 1 answer"
      must_has_correct_answer: "must has at least 1 correct answer"
  time_format: "%H:%M:%S"
  date_format: "%Y/%m/%d"
  datetime_format: "%Y-%m-%d %l:%M %p"
  edituser: "Edit User"
  updateuser: "Update Your Profile"
  settings: "Settings"
  allusers: "All Users"
  profileupdated: "Profile updated"
  pleaselogin: "Please log in"
  you_sure: "You sure?"
  user_deleted: "User deleted!"
  unsuccess: "Something gone wrong!"
  save_changes: "Save changes"
  controllers.admin.users.flash.success.delete_user: "Deleted user!"
  controllers.admin.users.flash.fail.delete_user: "Deleted fail!"
  controllers.application.flash.danger.invalid_user: "Invalid user!"
  subject_not_found: "Subject not found!"

